<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- generator="wordpress/2.0.2" --><rss version="0.92">
<channel>
	<title>Techcrunch</title>
	<link>http://www.techcrunch.com</link>
	<description>TechCrunch is a weblog dedicated to obsessively profiling and reviewing every newly launched web 2.0 business, product and service. We are part of the  Archimedes Ventures  Network of Companies.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2006 23:37:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss092</docs>
	<language>en</language>
	
	<item>
		<title>MingleNow to make top users VIPs in real life</title>
		<description>MingleNow is a place-centered social networking site that will offer real world incentives for online activity.  Incubated by advertising company BlueLithium, MingleNow will launch a limited beta early next week and open to the public at the end of this month.  I've been waiting for this to come ...</description>
		<link>http://www.techcrunch.com/2006/09/05/minglenow-to-make-top-users-vips-in-real-life/</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>New Facebook Redesign More Than Aesthetic</title>
		<description>Facebook launched two new features and a major design change tonight that affects all of their 9.5 million users. The new products, called News Feed and Mini Feed, are designed to change what Founder and CEO Mark Zuckerberg calls Facebook's old "Encyclopedic interface," where pages mostly just list off information ...</description>
		<link>http://www.techcrunch.com/2006/09/05/new-facebook-redesign-more-than-just-aesthetics/</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Very Early Look at Synthasite’s Ajax Website Builder</title>
		<description>South Africa based incuBeta will soon launch a website builder called Synthasite to help people build webpages entirely online. It will include a lot of the functionality of desktop applications like Frontpage and Dreamweaver (think Writely or Zoho Writer v. Word).

Like Sitekreator and Google Page Creator, Synthasite will be an ...</description>
		<link>http://www.techcrunch.com/2006/09/04/very-early-look-at-synthasites-ajax-website-builder/</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>A Moment to Say Thanks to our Sponsors</title>
		<description>Just a quick note to say Thank You to our six TechCrunch sponsors, as well as the companies that have listed job openings at the CrunchBoard job board. If you are interested in sponsoring the TechCrunch site, information is here. Our six sponsors are:


	Faces.com: Faces.com is a social network with ...</description>
		<link>http://www.techcrunch.com/2006/09/04/a-moment-to-say-thanks-to-our-sponsors/</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>ComBOTS is easy VOIP and file transfer for your avatars</title>
		<description>ComBOTS is a German company that has just taken its product to beta and appears aimed to carve a chunk out of Skype's potential customer base.  You'll have to get in line for an account right now but it's worth an early look at the site.  ComBOTS is ...</description>
		<link>http://www.techcrunch.com/2006/09/04/combots-aims-for-simplicity-in-voip-and-filesharing/</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>WebWorkerDaily, for the Web 2.0 Worker</title>
		<description>Om Malik's blog network is starting to take shape as he launches WebWorkerDaily this afternoon. The new site is a blog for the distributed worker, where the office is wherever their laptop happens to be. Cell phones, Skype, laptops and other tools have made it possible for an entire generation ...</description>
		<link>http://www.techcrunch.com/2006/09/04/webworkerdaily-for-the-web-20-worker/</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Geesee to offer cross-site chat by tag</title>
		<description>Geesee is an early stage startup from Slovakia that will combine topical web chat, tag search and widgets.  If you've seen MeeboMe, imagine instead a widget that connects a network of web chat rooms organized by tags with access points across many blogs and web pages.

Publishers who put a ...</description>
		<link>http://www.techcrunch.com/2006/09/04/geesee-to-offer-cross-site-chat-by-tag/</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>OpenBC Design Challenge - €10,000 Prize</title>
		<description>OpenBC is a Hamburg, Germany based professional social networking site that is often compared to LinkedIN. They were founded in late 2003, are profitable, and boast nearly 2 million members and 275 million page views per month.

Six weeks ago they launched an open design challenge for the new personal profile ...</description>
		<link>http://www.techcrunch.com/2006/09/04/openbc-design-challenge-e10000-prize/</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>An interview with investor Paul Graham of Y Combinator</title>
		<description>Paul Graham believes we're not in a bubble, that startups shouldn't worry about their business models and the best companies are the ones with potential to kill old monopolies.   Graham is a partner at Y Combinator, a Mountain View firm that invests in very early tech startups.  ...</description>
		<link>http://www.techcrunch.com/2006/09/02/an-interview-with-vc-paul-graham-of-ycombinator/</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>MySpace To Sell Music Through Snocap</title>
		<description>MySpace is getting into the music business. They announced today that they will allow nearly 3 million unsigned bands to sell their music directly to Myspace users. Snocap will provide the back end technology for the service. The agreement also includes performance-based warrants to purchase stock in SnoCap(Fox recently took ...</description>
		<link>http://www.techcrunch.com/2006/09/02/myspace-gets-into-music-biz/</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Is Browzar Just An Adware Machine?</title>
		<description>Earlier this week the big story was the launch of a new "safe" browser called Browzar, which InfoWorld called "the latest entrant to the crowded Internet browser market". 

Browzar promises to make web surfing more anonymous by disabling cookies, history, auto-complete, etc. The story was widely circulated, including writeups on ...</description>
		<link>http://www.techcrunch.com/2006/09/01/is-browzar-just-an-adware-machine/</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Partystrands aims to be Last.fm + Digg for the jukebox</title>
		<description>Partystrands is a music  service launching next month that will bring together aggregated recommendations, voting and photos synchronized on location by mobile phone.  Created by the Corvallis, Oregon and Barcelona, Spain based company MyStrands, PartyStrands is targeting bars and clubs.   The site will go live on ...</description>
		<link>http://www.techcrunch.com/2006/09/01/partystrands-aims-to-be-lastfm-digg-for-the-jukebox/</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Google Image Labeler Uses Human Labor</title>
		<description>Google Image Labeler launched today. It's a game, based on Luis von Ahn's ESP Game, that puts two random users together and asks them to label/tag an image. The idea is that if two people come up with the same label, it is probably a good one and will make ...</description>
		<link>http://www.techcrunch.com/2006/09/01/google-image-labeler/</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>iTunes To Have Movie Downloads This Month</title>
		<description>Rumors have been swirling for weeks (see here and here) that Apple will soon be selling full length movie downloads on the iTunes service. This morning, Business Week is stating, based on unnamed sources, that the service will launch by mid-September.

And adding color to the story: WalMart is pissed off.

Apple ...</description>
		<link>http://www.techcrunch.com/2006/09/01/itunes-to-have-movie-downloads-this-month/</link>
			</item>
	<item>
		<title>Microsoft Cries Foul At Stolen Interface</title>
		<description>Microsoft Expo's project leader, Garry Wiseman, wrote a blog post earlier today criticizing Sina, one of China's largest search engines, saying "Sina.com steals our design and graphics".

The post highlights the similar look and feel of Sina's new classifieds site to a previous release of Expo, including the identical color scheme ...</description>
		<link>http://www.techcrunch.com/2006/09/01/microsoft-cries-foul-at-stolen-interface/</link>
			</item>
</channel>
</rss><!-- Dynamic Page Served (once) in 0.595 seconds -->
