<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
			<channel>
			<title>Remote Synthesis</title>
			<link>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm</link>
			<description>Development using ColdFusion, Flash, SQL and more</description>
			<language>en-us</language>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2006 17:08:36 -0400</pubDate>
			<lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2006 20:41:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
			<generator>BlogCFC</generator>
			<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
			<managingEditor>brinaldi@remotesynthesis.com</managingEditor>
			<webMaster>brinaldi@remotesynthesis.com</webMaster>
			
			
			
			
			
			<item>
				<title>Contract ColdFusion Position in Downtown Boston</title>
				<link>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/30/Contract-ColdFusion-Position-in-Downtown-Boston</link>
				<description>
				
				This job posting is from Sara Jansen at Apex Systems for a 4-6 month contract position in downtown Boston, if you are interested please contact her via the phone number given below. Also, if you are looking for ColdFusion jobs in Boston, keep an eye on the Boston CFUG jobs board as I always post them there, though not always here.
				 [More]
				</description>
				
				<category>Boston CFUG</category>
				
				<category>ColdFusion</category>
				
				<pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2006 20:41:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<guid>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/30/Contract-ColdFusion-Position-in-Downtown-Boston</guid>
				
			</item>
			
		 	
			
			
			<item>
				<title>What's New In Mach ii 1.1.1 Presentation Recording</title>
				<link>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/29/Whats-New-In-Mach-ii-111-Presentation-Recording</link>
				<description>
				
				Matt Woodward and Peter Farrell presented today on "What's New in Mach ii 1.1.1" via Breeze. It was a great presentation, and Peter finally got to reveal the "secret" new feature which is application.cfc support. This will now give you access to onSessionStart/End(), onApplicationStart/End(), etc. Personally, I am already curious about using this feature since I was getting pretty comfortable using application.cfc before I started using frameworks. For anyone interested who missed the Breezo, you can view the recording here (note: there was some audio difficulty in the middle of the recording, but it was brief, so bear with it). Thanks to both Peter and Matt not only for this presentation, but also for all their hard work updating Mach ii.

As a side note, I am hoping to host further presentations on open-source projects like this one in the near future. If you are an author of an open-source project and are interested in presenting via Breeze, please contact me.
				
				</description>
				
				<category>ColdFusion</category>
				
				<category>Open-Source CF</category>
				
				<pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2006 13:10:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<guid>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/29/Whats-New-In-Mach-ii-111-Presentation-Recording</guid>
				
			</item>
			
		 	
			
			
			<item>
				<title>ColdFusion Open-Source Update - August 28</title>
				<link>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/28/ColdFusion-OpenSource-Update--August-28</link>
				<description>
				
				This was a busy week. A new beta of Mach ii was released and we added another 3 new open-source projects: Wininfo, gCal and Kalendar (funny there wasn't even a calendar category on the open-source list before two weeks ago and suddenly there are 3 projects in there).

Speaking of the list, I am moving along with a wholesale rewrite of it (built with mach ii and coldspring). In part this will be the first step to adding a bunch of new features. It is also a rework of the user interface. Along the user interface lines, I hope to post a "preview" (read - work in progress) sometime perhaps this week to get some feedback.
				 [More]
				</description>
				
				<category>Open-Source CF</category>
				
				<category>FarCry CMS</category>
				
				<category>ColdFusion</category>
				
				<pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2006 18:59:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<guid>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/28/ColdFusion-OpenSource-Update--August-28</guid>
				
			</item>
			
		 	
			
			
			<item>
				<title>What's New In Mach ii 1.1.1 Breeze Presentation</title>
				<link>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/24/Whats-New-In-Mach-ii-111-Breeze-Presentation</link>
				<description>
				
				As part of the Adobe Community Experts program I get a Breeze account. I am hoping to use this to feature presentations regarding open-source projects. The first of the presentations along these lines will be "What's New in Mach ii 1.1.1" featuring presenters Matt Woodward and Peter Farrell.

Matt and Peter have recently released the 1.1.1 update into beta which despite its not being a full point release, actually has some nice updates and new features. The presentation will be at 1pm EST on Tuesday, August 29th.

Please RSVP for the presentation by commenting on this blog post. Unfortunately, at this time, the Breeze account I have is limited to 15 people. So, unless that changes, I will have to limit live attendance to the first RSVPs (I am hoping to have this changed soon...if not, hopefully for future presos). Nonetheless, I will post a recording URL when the preso is done.

The presentation URL is http://experts.breezecentral.com/remotesynth/.
				
				</description>
				
				<category>Open-Source CF</category>
				
				<category>ColdFusion</category>
				
				<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2006 16:24:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<guid>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/24/Whats-New-In-Mach-ii-111-Breeze-Presentation</guid>
				
			</item>
			
		 	
			
			
			<item>
				<title>ColdFusion Open-Source Update - August 21</title>
				<link>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/21/ColdFusion-OpenSource-Update--August-21</link>
				<description>
				
				Bet ya thought I'd be late this week... Another week of new projects - 3 to be exact: Vivio Calendar, BlogCFC Atom and Sean's REST adapter. Keep 'em coming!

On a side-note, I have joined the CFDJ editorial board with a focus on promoting ColdFusion open-source projects (though my bio is conspicuously absent from the board page). Feel free to share any ideas with me on how I can best achieve that ends through CFDJ.
				 [More]
				</description>
				
				<category>ColdFusion</category>
				
				<category>Open-Source CF</category>
				
				<pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2006 14:24:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<guid>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/21/ColdFusion-OpenSource-Update--August-21</guid>
				
			</item>
			
		 	
			
			
			<item>
				<title>Samuel Rinaldi born August 17th</title>
				<link>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/17/Samuel-Rinaldi-born-August-17th</link>
				<description>
				
				My 2nd son, Samuel Efrain Rinaldi, was born at 12:00am last night weighing 6 pounds 9 ounces and with a very healthy cry :) Interestingly, he got his own birthday by a matter of seconds as my birhtday was yesterday and my wife's is tomorrow. If you want to see pictures, I will post to my Flickr account or on my about me page shortly (neither of which I have done a good job of maintaining I admit). I will also be doing my best to keep up with the open-source updates and lists the next couple weeks, but at least you might understand why I might fall behind.
				
				</description>
				
				<category>personal</category>
				
				<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2006 14:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<guid>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/17/Samuel-Rinaldi-born-August-17th</guid>
				
			</item>
			
		 	
			
			
			<item>
				<title>ColdFusion Open-Source Update - August 14</title>
				<link>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/14/ColdFusion-OpenSource-Update--August-14</link>
				<description>
				
				Another active week with few of the usual suspects. In fact, once again there are several new projects to announce including FlexMon, CodeCop, ColdSparx and some Red Ballon Labs projects. It is great to see the ColdFusion open source community growing rapidly, but man you guys are gonna eat up my Mondays so keep it at a measured pace ;) I need to add a few items to the list, but I will be listing over 120 projects, which is awesome considering that the original blog post back in december had less than 80 I believe...and also taking into account a considerable growth in new projects lately.
				 [More]
				</description>
				
				<category>ColdFusion</category>
				
				<category>Open-Source CF</category>
				
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2006 15:26:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<guid>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/14/ColdFusion-OpenSource-Update--August-14</guid>
				
			</item>
			
		 	
			
			
			<item>
				<title>Getting Started with Subclipse</title>
				<link>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/10/Getting-Started-with-Subclipse</link>
				<description>
				
				This is a help document I created for my coworkers on using Subclipse, but it may be helpful to others who are just getting started with Subclipse and Subversion. I have been using Subclipse for some time now, but I wouldn't necessarily consider myself an expert by any means. So, any Subclipse experts out there, please feel free to post your tips, corrections and/or advice.

Subclipse is a plugin for the Eclipse IDE that allows you to interact with your Subversion repositories using a visual IDE (as opposed to the standard svn command-line). It can be downloaded at http://subclipse.tigris.org.
				 [More]
				</description>
				
				<category>Subversion</category>
				
				<category>CFEclipse</category>
				
				<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2006 10:28:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<guid>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/10/Getting-Started-with-Subclipse</guid>
				
			</item>
			
		 	
			
			
			<item>
				<title>Objects and Frameworks - The Right Framework</title>
				<link>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/9/Objects-and-Frameworks--The-Right-Framework</link>
				<description>
				
				Inevitably when discussing getting started with frameworks, the question comes up, "Which framework should I choose?" Well, let's answer that.

You see, many years ago 4 frameworks were created and given to the gurus of ColdFusion OO. Then forged in the depths of Mordor was created the one framework to rule them all; one framework that could unleash the full power of ColdFusion. That framework was called...
				 [More]
				</description>
				
				<category>Open-Source CF</category>
				
				<category>ColdFusion</category>
				
				<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2006 21:24:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<guid>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/9/Objects-and-Frameworks--The-Right-Framework</guid>
				
			</item>
			
		 	
			
			
			<item>
				<title>ColdFusion Open-Source Update - August 7</title>
				<link>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/7/ColdFusion-OpenSource-Update--August-7</link>
				<description>
				
				Definitely not the usual suspects this week. We actually have a handful of new projects to discuss (including my own) and some general updates. Honestly, with all the releases happening lately, I am strongly in need of revamping the list - with 118 projects now and counting, it is getting a bit unwieldy as a just a huge list (granted you can filter, but by default you view all). However, this is a great problem to have; it seems like there is certainly no shortage of ColdFusion developers willing to share with the community.
				 [More]
				</description>
				
				<category>Open-Source CF</category>
				
				<category>ColdFusion</category>
				
				<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2006 13:56:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<guid>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/7/ColdFusion-OpenSource-Update--August-7</guid>
				
			</item>
			
		 	
			
			
			<item>
				<title>New Open-Source Component Generator</title>
				<link>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/3/New-OpenSource-Component-Generator</link>
				<description>
				
				Many months back, I wrote a post showing you how to create your own code generator using XSL stylesheets and the admin API for database introspection. There were a couple of issues with it: 1) the generated code sucked (hey, I was very new to the OO stuff) 2) it wasn't very extensible as everything was handled through a single template. Since then, I have had the opportunity to update the generator and am finally releasing it as the Illudium PU-36 Code Generator (any Looney Tunes fans out there?) as a new open-source project under an Apache 2.0 license. You can download the code via the Subversion repository by going here (note: I plan to have a project page on this site soon). Keep in mind, this is alpha software, so there are likely bugs in there.
				 [More]
				</description>
				
				<category>Programming</category>
				
				<category>Open-Source CF</category>
				
				<category>ColdFusion</category>
				
				<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2006 15:27:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<guid>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/3/New-OpenSource-Component-Generator</guid>
				
			</item>
			
		 	
			
			
			<item>
				<title>Avoiding eval() and iif()</title>
				<link>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/2/Avoiding-eval-and-iif</link>
				<description>
				
				I am not sure if I have posted this before (I am sure others have), but I thought I might mention a simple tip that doesn't seem obvious at all. Basically, you can put simple statements between pound signs and they will get evaluated. For instance, I used to do something like this in my queryparam's:





However, I have changed - and simplified - that to:





The "not len()" gets evaluated to true if the item has a length of 0 or false if it has any value other than empty string without the need for the iif statement or even an eval statement.

This is the most useful (to me) aspect of this "shortcut," but you can also do things like this:





Notice that the content of the file attribute does the string concatenation within a single set of pound signs. Yes, this only saves a few keystrokes, but I also find it easier to read (I've always found that the pound signs can clutter a page personally).

I would say that I have no idea if there are any negative performance consequences involved here (either positive or negative) since I haven't tested for that (in the places I have used this, if there were I didn't notice them)...plus if I got into that, Peter Bell might get on me about the dangers of "premature optimization." ;)
				
				</description>
				
				<category>Programming</category>
				
				<category>ColdFusion</category>
				
				<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2006 12:27:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<guid>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/8/2/Avoiding-eval-and-iif</guid>
				
			</item>
			
		 	
			
			
			<item>
				<title>ColdFusion Open-Source Update - July 31</title>
				<link>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/7/31/ColdFusion-OpenSource-Update--July-31</link>
				<description>
				
				A lot of framework activity this week, including the release of Fusebox 5. Mach-II, Model-Glue and ColdBox each offer us some updated information on their upcoming releases. Also, Andrea Veggiani released a new beta of AVBlog that includes a number of interesting new features that are worth checking out.
				 [More]
				</description>
				
				<category>Open-Source CF</category>
				
				<category>ColdFusion</category>
				
				<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2006 14:43:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<guid>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/7/31/ColdFusion-OpenSource-Update--July-31</guid>
				
			</item>
			
		 	
			
			
			<item>
				<title>Aptana Eclipse-Based Web IDE</title>
				<link>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/7/31/Aptana-EclipseBased-Web-IDE</link>
				<description>
				
				You may have heard about this on the latest ColdFusion Weekly Podcast (I actually found this on dzone), but Aptana is a new IDE based on Eclipse that offers code assist on JavaScript, HTML, and CSS. The CSS code assist alone is huge to me since I have not found a decent CSS editor for Eclipse up to now. The code assist will even let you know the compatibility (Firefox/IE) of the attribute. I am just beginning to test this out, but for the moment it seems like an excellent compliment to CFEclipse.
				
				</description>
				
				<category>CFEclipse</category>
				
				<category>CSS</category>
				
				<category>General</category>
				
				<category>JavaScript</category>
				
				<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2006 12:24:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<guid>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/7/31/Aptana-EclipseBased-Web-IDE</guid>
				
			</item>
			
		 	
			
			
			<item>
				<title>New Google Code Hosting</title>
				<link>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/7/27/New-Google-Code-Hosting</link>
				<description>
				
				Caught this on Digg, but Google has launched a code hosting project. It includes a project workspace, version cotrol via Subversion, issue tracking and mailing lists. It is also open to any open-source project. Currently there are only two ColdFusion projects listed there - CFWheels and GoogleCheckoutCFC - but worth keeping tabs on.
				
				</description>
				
				<category>ColdFusion</category>
				
				<category>Open-Source CF</category>
				
				<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2006 20:20:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<guid>http://www.remotesynthesis.com/blog/index.cfm/2006/7/27/New-Google-Code-Hosting</guid>
				
			</item>
			
		 	
			</channel></rss>
