<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Config>
    <Application>ColdBox Dashboard</Application>
    <Version>2.2.4</Version>
    <Filename>../builds/dashboard_2.2.4.zip</Filename>
    <UpdateDate>December 20 2008</UpdateDate>
    <Author>Luis Majano</Author>
    <Description><![CDATA[********************************************************************************Copyright 2005-2008 Luis Majano and Ortus Solutions, Corpwww.luismajano.com | www.ortussolutions.com********************************************************************************HONOR GOES TO GOD ABOVE ALL********************************************************************************"Love must be sincere. Hate what is evil; cling to what is good. Be devoted to one another in brotherly love. Honor one another above yourselves. Never be lacking in zeal, but keep your spiritual fervor, serving the Lord. Be joyful in hope, patient in affliction, faithful in prayer. Share with God's people who are in need. Practice hospitality." Romans 12:9********************************************************************************WELCOME TO THE COLDBOX DASHBOARD LITE EDITION********************************************************************************Welcome To The ColdBox Dashboard Lite EditionCopyright by Luis Majano and Ortus Solutions, Corp********************************************************************************COLDBOX DASHBOARD LITE EDITION LICENSE********************************************************************************The ColdBox ColdBox Lite Edition is a separate application and entity from the ColdBoxFramework. The ColdBox Framework is free and open-source via the Apache 2license. The ColdBox Dashboard Lite Edition is free but not open source. You cannot use any code in this application for commercial or non-commercial usage. This application is exclusive property of Luis Majano and Ortus Solutions, Corp.However, you can use the application in your commercial or non-commercial productsAS IS, with no modifications,alterations or any indication of ownership alterations.If you would like to use the source code in the ColdBox Dashboard or modify it for yourown products commercial or non-commercial, then you will have to contact the saidowner so a special license can be arranged. Whether it may be provisional orpaid for.Please note that if you use this application, you are bound to this license.********************************************************************************COLDBOX DASHBOARD LITE EDITION INSTALLATION********************************************************************************You can also place the dashboard in any location of your web root if needed. The dashboard requires that ColdBox be installed in the default location of thewebroot as it is also a ColdBox Application. However, if you have refactoredthe ColdBox framework to your custom needs, you will need to alter some configurationin order for the Dashboard application to work:1) Application.cfc - Alter the extends property from coldbox.system.coldbox to 				     whatever location you choose.2) coldbox.xml.cfm - Alter the coldbox_location setting to point to the coldbox                    system folder. DO NOT APPEND A / AT THE END.      Example: /frameworks/coldbox_2 is the new location   <Setting name="Coldbox_Location" value="/frameworks/coldbox_2/coldbox/system"/>3) Open the handlers/baseHandler.cfc and change the extends to match your installation.Then reach it by going to the following address if in the default location:http://localhost/coldbox/dashboardThe default password is coldbox********************************************************************************SYSTEM REQUIREMENTS********************************************************************************- ColdFusion MX 7.X and above- BlueDragon 7.X and above- Railo 2.0 and above- Application Scope for the Frameworks internal structures- Session Scope for messaging and other features********************************************************************************CHANGELOG********************************************************************************Version 2.2.4New application generation engineResource Cleanups and Updates.Version 2.2.3#15 Ability to generate application's outside of the webroot#21 ie7 layout problems#25 SES routing enabled - not build for ses#26 Application Template update from old code.#27 Update to latest Jquery#28 Update Resource Links#29 Document API - Not showing all directories#30 Update API look & feel#31 Update services to populate from RC#33 Scrollable toolbar not showing on modal for server viewer#34 Distribution webservice logic update#35 Update webservice to take in bug reports#36 JS modal standardization.#37 Debugger Settings Panel#38 Updates to comply to ColdBox 2.6.0#39 Ability to generate mxunit or cfcunit test cases#40 New Dashboard Logo#43	using the app generator in the dashboard, the config file has an incorrect value for the default view.Version 2.2.2- Minor updates to make it 2.5.0 complaint.- Next version will have major updates.  Version 2.2.1- #16 Update for max archives setting in logger.- #17 Removal of buffer setting- #18 Update of application template- #19 Help Files Updated   - #20 Jquery updated to version 1.1.3.1Version 2.2.0- Railo/BD Enhacned Support- ColdBox Path can be now changed.- Base Event handler for customization, not compiled.- App Generator updates, does now test suites and more.- Cleanup and optimization.Version 2.1.0- #1 Domain Model refactoring- #2 Addition of Framework Conventions- #3 Application GeneratorVersion 2.0.0- Update to the 2.0 ColdBox framework- Moved to JQuery********************************************************************************THE DAILY BREAD********************************************************************************"I am the way, and the truth, and the life; no one comes to the Father, but by me (JESUS)"Jn 14:1-12"Anyone who drinks the water I give will never thirst— not ever. The water I give will be an artesian spring within, gushing fountains of endless life."Jn 4:14******************************************************************************]]></Description>
</Config>