<rollovers>
   
    <section id="home">
        <rollover id="sysinfo">Displays the framework's and system's information</rollover>
        <rollover id="onlineresources">An extensive online resource list where you can find more useful information about ColdBox</rollover>
        <rollover id="cfcdocs">Creates the on the fly documentation for the framework's cfc's</rollover>
    </section>
    
    <section id="settings">
        <rollover id="frameworksettings">Displays the framework's read only settings</rollover>
        <rollover id="logfilesettings">From here you can change the coldbox logging facility's parameters</rollover>
        <rollover id="encodingsettings">From here you can change the file encoding to use when using the fileutilities plugin.</rollover>
        <rollover id="passwordsettings">Change your dashboard password, securely!!</rollover>
        <rollover id="proxysettings">Change your proxy settings, if needed.</rollover>
    </section>
     
    <section id="tools">
        <rollover id="appbuilder">Launches the ColdBox application builder wizard.</rollover>
        <rollover id="cfcgenerator">Your very own cfc generator based on Brian Rinaldi's Illidium Generator</rollover>
        <rollover id="logviewer">Lanuches ColdBox very own log viewer application.</rollover>
        <!--AppBuilder-->
        <rollover id="appname">Launches the ColdBox application builder wizard.</rollover>
        <rollover id="appmapping">The application mapping. This can be either relative to the web root or using a coldfusion mapping. You can also browse for it by clicking on the folder icon.</rollover>
        <rollover id="debugmode">Flag that determines if the ColdBox debugging will be carried out. This can slow down your application due to the timers and the rendering of the debugging screen. Use only for development.</rollover>
        <rollover id="debugpassword">The password you will use to go into debug mode or out if activating from the url action.</rollover>  
        <rollover id="enabledumpvar">Flag that determines if you can use the 'dumpvar' url action to dump variables in debug mode.</rollover>
        <rollover id="udflibraryfile">The location relative from the application root or using cfmx mappings of a udf template to load on all views, layouts and event handlers.</rollover>
        <rollover id="messageboxstyleclass">The css class name to use when rendering the messagebox. This class has to be loaded on your stylesheet. Look at the /coldbox/system/includes/messagebox.cfm for a template css.</rollover>
        <rollover id="defaultlayout">The default layout template to use for your application. This will be generated since you are starting a new project. The name choosen is just a best practice.</rollover>
        <rollover id="coldboxlogging">Flag that determines if the application will use the embedded ColdBox logging facility. If you select ENABLED make sure you fill out the location.</rollover>
        <rollover id="coldboxlogslocations">The location of where ColdBox will store your log file. This is either relative from your application root or an absolute path.</rollover>
        <rollover id="coldfusionlogging">Flag that determines wether to use the coldfusion logging facilities or not.</rollover>
        <rollover id="maineventhandler">The main event handler that will be auto generated for you according to the methods you select below.</rollover>   
   
    </section>  
    
    <section id="update">
        <rollover id="appbuilder">Launches the ColdBox application builder wizard.</rollover>
    </section>  
    
    <section id="bugs">
        <rollover id="submitbug">Submit a new bug to the offical bug email address.</rollover>
        <rollover id="tracdatabase">Visit the official Trac bug database and run ticket reports, view progress, etc.</rollover>
    </section>   
    
     
</rollovers>